copious.com 2013-05-21

# Copious | Copious Privacy Policy

##  Purpose of Policy

###  Utah Street Labs, Inc., Copious.com, and Copious (collectively "us", "we," or "Company") are committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Copious.com site (the "Site"). We created this Privacy Policy (this "Policy") to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This policy describes the ways we collect, store, use and protects your personal information. You accept this policy when you visit Copious.com. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy. You have rights under California Civil Code Section 1798.83, which protect and govern your personal information as disclosed by us; to exercise those rights, contact info@copious.com We may amend this policy at any time by posting a revised version on our Site. The revised version will be effective at the time we post it.

###  Data You Provide Us.

###  Account Data. You provide us with some personal data to create your account (or, we might get that data from a third party co-branded partner or other vendor). You can also tell us more about yourself via your Copious account pages or elsewhere, such as Facebook Connect. We may give you choices about whether to publish specific items of account data to everyone, your friends, or just yourself. In addition to displaying account data in connection with your account's public profile and your public activity on the Site, we use account data for many purposes, which may include internal or external efforts of Copious to improve the Site, generate reports of aggregated activity that we share with others, target ads to you or other users, and send emails to you or other users. Typically, you can turn our emails on and off, but our administrative emails are mandatory so long as you have an account. If you register through a co-branded site, we might share your account data with the cobrand partner, in which case your data is governed by that entity's privacy policies, not ours.

###  Content and Ratings. Our site allows you to publish content. Our Terms of Service [link] describes how we and our licensees may republish (or stop publishing) your content. We may publish some or all account data with your content (but if we have asked for your preferences, we will honor them). We may publish your product/review/other ratings, license the ratings to others, and use the ratings to develop aggregate ratings, personalize site views, merchandise products and identify/feature popular members or reviews.

###  Interest in Third Party Offerings. You may have opportunities to express interest in, or register for, third parties' offerings. If you do, we will follow your instructions about providing your data to the third party (and we may retain the data as well).

###  Surveys. Unless otherwise specified at a survey's beginning, we treat your survey responses like we treat our other business records.

###  Accessing Your Records. The information described in California Business & Professions Code Sec. 1798.83 is available by submitting the statutorily required information to info@copious.com

###  Data We Collect Automatically.

###  As part of our servers' normal operations, we log your IP address and referring/destination URLs. We may use this data and other server usage data to analyze site and user behavior, improve the Site, troubleshoot technical problems, resolve disputes, address complaints and generate reports of aggregated activity that we share with others. We and our third party vendors (such as our web analytics service provider) may use cookies and web beacons to analyze site usage, improve the Site, target ads, store your preferences/passwords (if you have registered), personalize your experience (including tracking your site usage to do so) and generate reports of aggregated activity that we share with others. You must accept cookies to access copious.com as a registered user.

###  Other Data Collection.

###  We may get data from or about you in other ways not specifically described in this statement. For example, you might contact Customer Service, or we may get a third party complaint about you. We handle this data like other business records.

###  Data Changes.

###  To the extent we permit you to modify or delete your data or content, we usually update our live databases immediately, but some data may update more slowly, and some old data may remain indefinitely in our archives and records. Also, we may be unable to propagate changes to partners who receive your data or content.

###  Contractors/Service Providers.

###  Third party contractors or other entities with which we work may have access to our databases. Usually these contractors or entities sign a standard confidentiality agreement. Some of our site's functionality may be operated by third party service providers, and in the course of providing this functionality, these service providers may obtain some of your personal data from you directly or transferred from us to facilitate your usage of the Service. Usually we require these providers to use and disclose your personal data only as necessary to perform their services. Third party ad servers may place or recognize a cookie and, using the cookie or otherwise, collect and use data from your visits to this and other websites to serve ads to you.

###  Notice concerning children.

###  Children under the age of 13 are not allowed to use the Service. We understand and are committed to respecting the sensitive nature of children's privacy online. If we learn or have reason to suspect that a site user is under the age of 13, we will promptly delete any personal information in that user's account

###  Our "Corporate Family."

###  We may share your data with any parent company, subsidiaries, joint ventures, other entities under a common control or third party acquirers. We expect these other entities will honor this statement. Also, we may allow a potential acquirer or merger partner to review our databases, although we would restrict their use and disclosure of this data during the diligence phase.

###  Government Relations and Lawsuits.

###  We may disclose data about you to the government if we are required to do so or if we think the disclosure is appropriate; and you authorize these disclosures. We may also disclose data about you in connection with actual or potential legal proceedings (a) if we are required to do so, (b) if such disclosures might mitigate our liability, or (c) to enforce our rights.

###  Communicating with Other Users.

###  You may not collect (manually or in an automated manner) other users' personal data (including email addresses) from the Site.

###  Limits on Our Abilities.

###  Our Site is very complicated, so we might inadvertently use or disclose your data in ways inconsistent with this statement. For example, a temporary software glitch could lead to public display of your personal data despite your contrary preferences. We might also make ad hoc uses of your data in ways not mentioned here. In these anomalous situations, your sole remedy is that we will try to rectify the anomaly as soon as we can.

###  Security.

###  We use industry-standard security protocols, such as (if and where we think appropriate) firewalls and restrictions on which employees can access user data. However, perfect security does not exist on the Internet.

###  Amendment.

###  This Privacy Policy is part of the Copious Terms of Service and can be modified in accordance with the amendment procedures described in that document.
